[
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Hg is the chemical symbol for which element?",
    "Answer": "mercury"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who was the scientist to propose the Laws of Motion?",
    "Answer": "Isaac Newton"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q3",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Animals that eat both plants and meat are called what?",
    "Answer": "omnivores"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q4",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which is the hottest planet in the solar system?",
    "Answer": "Venus"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q5",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who was the scientist to propose the General Theory of Relativity?",
    "Answer": "Albert Einstein"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q6",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the smallest unit of matter?",
    "Answer": "atom"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q7",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the smallest unit of life?",
    "Answer": "cell"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q8",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the element Pb?",
    "Answer": "lead"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q14",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "98deg Celcius is the boiling point of water H20",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q15",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "You can hear anything in outer space?",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q16",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Your hair and your nails are made from the same material.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q17",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "HTTP means Hypertext Transmission Protocol.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q18",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The name of Apple's desktop operating system is called Mac OS.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q19",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": ".xls is a file extension used in MS Word.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q20",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "UV stands for UltraViolet.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q21",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "If E=Mc2 according to Einstein, what does M stand for?",
    "Answer": "Mass"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q22",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What o is the earths atmospheric layer being destroyed by aerosols?",
    "Answer": "Ozone"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q24",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In physics, what does DC stand for?",
    "Answer": "Direct Current"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q40",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Name the worlds largest ocean.",
    "Answer": "Pacific"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q41",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which astrological signs symbol is a crab?",
    "Answer": "Cancer"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q42",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is a group of lions called?",
    "Answer": "pride"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q43",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the last color a rainbow ROYGBIV?",
    "Answer": "violet"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q44",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who was the first American president?",
    "Answer": "George Washington"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q45",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who was the first Philippine president?",
    "Answer": "Emilio Aguinaldo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q46",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who was the first woman Philippine president?",
    "Answer": "Corazon Aquino"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q47",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which zodiac sign is called The Maiden?",
    "Answer": "Virgo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q54",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Cornea is the part of the human eye that controls the amount of light that passes through the pupil.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q55",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "In chess, a bishop can move diagonally.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q56",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The Eiffel Tower is in Germany.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q57",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Japanese alphabet has two types, Katakana and Hiragana.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q58",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "UST has a lion as their university mascot.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q59",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Japanese sake is made from rice.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q60",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Smirnoff mule is a beer.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q20",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Optics is the study of what?",
    "Answer": "Light"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q21",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which computer company invented the first floppy disks, hard disk drives, and DRAMS?",
    "Answer": "IBM"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q22",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In what type of matter are atoms most tightly packed?",
    "Answer": "solid"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q23",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What instrument is used to measure wind speed?",
    "Answer": "anemometer"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q33",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Chloroplasts can be found in animal cells.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q34",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Rainforests are considered temperate climate regions.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q35",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The graduated cylinder is a tool thats used to measure fluid volume.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q36",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Gregorie Mendel is considered the founder of the modern science of genetics?",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q37",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Johannes Kepler best known for Laws of Thermodynamics.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q38",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Helium becomes a superfluid when cooled to absolute zero.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q39",
    "Category": "Science",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Spiders have 6 legs",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q61",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What musical term is indicates a chord where the notes are played one after another rather than all together?",
    "Answer": "Arpeggio"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q62",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What color does gold leaf appear if you hold it up to the light?",
    "Answer": "Green"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q63",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the capital city of Paraguay?",
    "Answer": "Asuncion"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q64",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which instrument is associated with Earl Powell?",
    "Answer": "Piano"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q65",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In a Glossectomy, which body part is removed?",
    "Answer": "tongue"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q66",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Elon Musk is the CEO of which famous brand?",
    "Answer": "Tesla"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q67",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the technical term for a lie detector?",
    "Answer": "polygraph"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q68",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which is the hardest natural substance found on earth?",
    "Answer": "diamond"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q75",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Two atomic bombs were dropped in Nagasaki and Hiroshima Japan.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q76",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The first person to step on the moon was Galileo Galilei.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q77",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The sun in the Milky Way galaxy is considered a star.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q78",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Lightyear is a measure of time.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q79",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "When in Norway, you can go visit the city of Stockholm.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q80",
    "Category": "GeneralInfo",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Mount Everest is located in Nepal.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q81",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the perimeter of a circle called?",
    "Answer": "circumference"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q82",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which number is greater, a googol, or a quadrillion?",
    "Answer": "googol"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q83",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is an angle called if its greater than 90 degrees?",
    "Answer": "obtuse"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q84",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the top number of a fraction called?",
    "Answer": "numerator"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q85",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is a shape with eight sides called?",
    "Answer": "octagon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q86",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the roman numeral for number 19?",
    "Answer": "xix"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q87",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Does a convex shape curve inward or outward?",
    "Answer": "outward"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q88",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the basic metric unit of mass?",
    "Answer": "gram"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q89",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the basic metric unit of length?",
    "Answer": "meter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q90",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "A formula for the area of a circle can be written as (pi)Rsquared, what is R?",
    "Answer": "radius"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q91",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who formulated the Pythagorean Theorem?",
    "Answer": "Pythagoras"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q98",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Zero is the only number that doesnt have its own Roman numeral.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q99",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Two is not the only even prime number.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q100",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Pi is a rational number.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q101",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "All sides are equal in an Isosceles triangle.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q102",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Negative four is a natural number.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q103",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "100 is greater than 10 squared.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q104",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The number 28 is a whole number.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q139",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which Former NBA Player Was Nicknamed Agent Zero?",
    "Answer": "Gilbert Arenas"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q140",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "The character of Cyclops is romantically linked to what other character in the X-Men universe?",
    "Answer": "Jean Grey"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q141",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In The Matrix, does Neo take the blue or red pill?",
    "Answer": "red"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q142",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In the film series Harry Potter, what is the wizarding sport played on broomsticks?",
    "Answer": "quidditch"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q143",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In Marvel films, what is the name of the actor who portrayed the character of Captain America?",
    "Answer": "Chris Evans"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q144",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In the series The Office, who is the regional branch manager of Scranton branch?",
    "Answer": "Michael Scott"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q145",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In the film Zootopia, what kind of animal is Judy Hopps?",
    "Answer": "rabbit"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q152",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Arthur Doyle created Sherlock Holmes.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q153",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Robbie Coltrane, who plays Hagrid in the Harry Potter films, was the first actor to be cast in the series.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q154",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "In the series Game of Thrones, Jon Snow became the king of Westeros.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q155",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Kelly Clarkson was the very first American Idol winner.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q156",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Billie Eilish is obsessed with the classic TV show The Office.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q157",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Sandra Bullock played the character of Emily in the film series Emily in Paris.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q121",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which Avenger other than Captain America was able to pick up Thors Mjolnir in the Marvel movies?",
    "Answer": "vision"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q122",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In little red riding hood, who does the wolf dress up as?",
    "Answer": "grandmother"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q123",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who is the half-blood prince in Harry Potter?",
    "Answer": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q124",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Wolverine has been played by what Australian actor in the X-Men films spanning from 2000-2017?",
    "Answer": "Hugh Jackman"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q125",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who was the fictional character Shrek marries in his titular film series?",
    "Answer": "Fiona"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q126",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "In the game Mobile Legends:Bang Bang, who has the ability to turn opponents to a cat?",
    "Answer": "nana"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q127",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Which Marvel movies soundtrack won two Grammys?",
    "Answer": "Black Panther"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q133",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "J.K Rowling is the famous author of the Harry Potter book series.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q134",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "In films, Tom Holland is the second actor who portrayed the role of Spider-Man.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q135",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Silent Sanctuary popularized the song Imahe",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q136",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Legend of Korra is the sequel of the cartoon series Avatar: Legend of Aang",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q137",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "In the anime series Death Note, Kira is also Light Yagami",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q138",
    "Category": "Entertainment",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Benedict Cumberbatch portrayed the character of John Watson in the series film, Sherlock Holmes.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q105",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the name of the longest side of a right-angled triangle?",
    "Answer": "hypotenuse"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q106",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What do you call the circles with the same center?",
    "Answer": "concentric"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q107",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What mathematical word is used to indicate the likelihood of something to occur?",
    "Answer": "probability"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q108",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Understanding and describing change is a common theme in the natural sciences, and what was developed as a powerful tool to investigate it?",
    "Answer": "calculus"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q109",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "Who is the father of Mathematics?",
    "Answer": "Archimedes"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q115",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Hologram is a flat image that can be displayed in three dimensions.",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q116",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "A hexadecagon is a geometric form that does not have any vertices.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q117",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "Eudemus wrote an elaborate history of Greek Geometry from its earliest origins?",
    "Answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q118",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The derivative of tanx is secx/tanx.",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q119",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The integral of sinx is cotx+C",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q120",
    "Category": "Math",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "QuestionType": "TrueFalse",
    "Question": "The integral of hyperbolic function cothx dx is ln(coshx)+C",
    "Answer": "false"
  }
]